I'm going to play you two videos. You got to watch both of them. And you're only going to
find value in this if you think it means something to be lied to about why your gas prices are up.
And so I want you to watch this. And then I want you to think about if they're lying to us about
why the gas prices are up, then what do we do to respond to them lying to us? I do have to level
with people. This will not be easy. It is now clear that the impact of this war will affect the future
of our country. The war in the Middle East has caused the biggest spike in petrol and diesel
prices in history. Australia is not an active participant in this war, but all Australians
are paying higher prices because of it. If you can switch to catching the train or bus
or tram to work, do so. That builds our reserves and it saves fuel for people who have no choice
but to drive. The months ahead may not be easy. The next part of the challenge that we were facing
was the supply and the pricing of petroleum products. Our authorities are all continuing to find new
resources for the supply. And although we cannot be assured right now of the supply, we can be sure
that at least for 45 days we will be alright.
All right.
Efficiency mobilitas, termasuk pembatasan penggunaan kendaraan dinas, 50%, kecuali untuk operasional
and kendaraan listrik, dan mendorong penggunaan transportasi publik. Untuk memastikan distribusi BBM,
BBM, pemerintah akan melakukan...
Mayor General Neil McCaslan left an open book on X, and no one is reading his tweets. Think about who
this man is. He didn't just work for the Air Force, he ran the Air Force Research Lab. He was the
gatekeeper for Pentagon's most sensitive special access programs. Then on February 27th, he walks out
his new Mexico home and just vanishes. Ten days before he disappeared, the military pulled a massive PR
stunt called Operation Windlord. They used C-17s to transport micronuclear reactors across the country.
The news calls it clean energy revolution, but McCaslan, he posted one word, idiocracy. He was
trying to tell us that while they're disclosing micronukes to the plebs, us, they are hiding the
discovery that makes nuclear power look like a campfire. McCaslan wrote that electricity can be
for free. He explained that a lightning bolt isn't just weather, it's a non-linear discharge of an
adiabatic field that is always flowing around us. He's talking about tapping into the Earth's own
magnetosphere. He's telling us that this energy crisis is manufactured lie to keep us all paying
for the fuel while the government harvests the sky for free. He goes deeper. He talks about the 2DOF
lattice, a forbidden state of physics where mass loses its grip on reality. He says if you sink an ion
in an electron wave at a massoscopic interface, you don't take off with engines, you float away.
No inertia. No g-forces. It's the technology he was overseeing before he was unplugged.
This explains why we see a craft making 90 degree turns that should liquefy the human pilot.
And here is the something dark part. McCaslan is just one of the 9 top level American scientists
who have disappeared or died in the last year. Most were tied to the Air Force Research Lab.
In the three addresses yesterday by Trump Starmer and Albanese talked about national resiliency and fuel
fines. They want us scared and dependent on the grid. McCaslan's open book is the only thing
standing between us and an engineered dark age. Do your research yourself. His ex account is still up.
So we understand that the energy crisis is just created. So why? Why are there scarcities that are
created? And this is where we have to employ our critical thinking. Scarcities are created because once
you have a scarcity, you can actually manipulate the response to that. You can manipulate the funds that are
applied to that. You can manipulate the, uh, the violence, the war that's applied to that, et cetera.
Right now, there's a scarcity in oil because a literal war was started via two members of a
European banking conglomerate, the United States and Israel, and the Strait of Hormuz, which is where
the oil that was coming from is now not coming, was open. They created a situation that created a
scarcity. And now they're telling you that you need to suffer through that scarcity and that they're
going to figure it out. What they're doing is creating a scenario where you now are trusting
your government. And if you trust your government, then you will, then you will let them do anything,
even if it's going to harm you. That's what's happening right now.
Why would you trust the government that's lying to you in order to get you to trust them?